https://www.cigarhumidors-online.com/cheap-cigars-humidors-support/privacy.html

Hygrometer Calibration
Treatment (Mold)
Treatment (Tobacco Beetles)
Shopping Cart
Shopping Cart ( 0 ) There are no products in your shopping cart.
Home
»
Privacy Policy - 1st Class Cigar Humidors
Privacy Policy
What information do we collect? We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously
What do we use your information for? Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs) To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you) To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
To process transactions your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested. To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature To send periodic emails The email address you provide for order processing, will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order.
How do we protect your information? We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or access your personal information. We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.
Do we use cookies? Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits, and keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still place orders over the telephone or by contacting customer service.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties? We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. We may release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety.
California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance: Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.
Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance: We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 21 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 21 years old or older. Online Privacy Policy Only This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.
Terms and Conditions: Please also visit our Customer Service section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website. Your consent by using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.
Changes to our Privacy Policy: If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. This policy was last modified on April 14, 2011
Contacting Us: If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may reach us by clicking on the "contact us" link.
Home
Humidors
All Humidors
Small Humidors
Medium Humidors
Large Humidors
Travel Humidors
Cabinet Humidors
Join our Mailing List
Receive special promotions & discounts & sign me up for a chance to win a Free Humidor
Sign Me Up!
Spend $75 on Cigar Accessories and Your Order Ships FREE!This offer applies to Continental US ground shipments only.  Excludes PO Boxes/APO, oversized items, cigar cabinets, end tables & cigars.
.
Money Back Guarantee
Fantastic Prices
No Sales Tax (Except FL)
Our guarantee is simple and straight forward.  We offer our customers a 30 day unconditional money back guarantee.
Shipping Policy
We ship all our orders within two business days or less. Get more information about our shipping policies.
Customer Service
Feel free to browse through our customer service section.  We are here to answer all your questions and concerns.
Cigar Blog
Our Article Archive & Cigar Blog features useful information, news, entertainment and commentary on humidors and cigars.
Huge Selection
See our line of beautifully crafted & exclusive cigar humidors. We are certain you will not find accessories like these for less!
Connect with Us:
1650 NW 18th Street - Unit 801, Pompano Beach, FL 33069
Phone:
954-975-2499 or 888-396-6838 9:30am to 6:30pm Monday - Friday  (EST)
Contact | Privacy Policy © Copyright 1997-2020 cigarhumidors-online.com
loading...
